I'm Peppa Pig. [snorts]
-This is my little brother, George.
-[snorts]
-This is Mommy Pig.
-[Mommy Pig snorts]
And this is Daddy Pig.
-[Daddy Pig snorts]
-[all laugh]
Peppa Pig. [snorts]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] Peppa and her friends
are playing at Rebecca Rabbit's house.
[all giggling]
[woofs] Let's play hide-and-seek.
[bleats] We'll all hide,
and Peppa can find us.
Okay. One, two...
[narrator] Everyone must find
a hiding place before Peppa counts to ten.
Danny and Candy are hiding
in the branches of a little tree.
Zoë, Pedro and Rebecca are hiding
behind a fence.
Suzy and Emily are hiding behind a bush.
...nine, ten!
Ready or not, here I come!
[giggles] I know where you are.
Oh!
[giggling]
Oh.
[narrator] Peppa cannot find anyone.
[sighs] This is impossible.
[bell dings]
[narrator] Freddy Fox has come to play.
[snorts] Hello, Freddy.
[barks] Hello, Peppa. What are you doing?
We're playing hide-and-seek.
But I can't find anyone.
Shall I find them for you?
You can try, but it's impossible.
[barks] Watch this.
[Freddy sniffing]
-Found you.
-[all] Oh! Hello, Freddy.
-Aha! There you are!
-[both] Oh.
-Boo!
-[both] Oh!
[narrator] Freddy Fox has found everyone.
How did you do that?
I'm good at smelling.
What's smelling got to do with it?
I can find you by sniffing your smell.
[bleats] I'm not smelly.
I had a bath last night.
I know. You smell nice.
Oh. [giggles]
[barks] I could even find you
with my eyes closed.
Go on, then. [snorts]
Find Suzy with your eyes closed.
Easy.
Hide, Suzy.
[all] One, two, three, four...
[narrator] Suzy is looking
for somewhere to hide.
...six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ready or not, here I come. [sniffing]
[narrator] Freddy is looking for Suzy
with his eyes closed.
He is sniffing
where Suzy Sheep has walked:
round the tree...
behind the little bush...
and back up the hill.
-Found you!
-[Suzy] Oh! [giggles]
All thanks to my nose.
It's a super nose!
Yes, it is.
Has everything got a smell?
Oh, yes. Everything has a different smell.
What do I smell of?
[Freddy sniffs]
You smell of flowers and Wellington boots.
[all laugh]
What do I smell of?
[sniffs] You smell of wet grass
and biscuits.
[all laugh]
What do I smell of?
-[sniffs] Bananas and jam.
-[laughs]
What do I smell of?
-[sniffs] Milk and fish fingers.
-[laughs]
What do I smell of?
[sniffs] Pedro, you smell of toothpaste.
Oh.
What's your favorite smell?
Eggs.
What is the worst thing
you've ever smelled?
Blue cheese.
[all] Pooey! [laugh]
[sniffs]
It's nearly dinnertime.
How do you know?
I can smell carrot soup.
[all sniff]
I can smell carrot soup, too.
[all] And me!
Dinner's ready!
Come and get your carrot soup.
[all giggling]
[narrator] Everyone is enjoying
Mommy Rabbit's carrot soup.
This soup is yummy.
-[horn honks outside]
-Who can that be?
[narrator] Mr. Fox has come
to take Freddy home.
[sniffs] Mm.
I can smell dinner.
Oh, Mr. Fox. Hello.
Hello, Mommy Rabbit.
Hello, Dad. I've just had my dinner
down a rabbit hole.
Good lad.
And can you guess what's for pudding?
[sniffs] Smells nice. [sniffs]
I'd say strawberry jelly.
That's right!
[narrator] Mr. Fox loves smelling things.
[all sniff]
[children] Mm.
[narrator] Everyone loves smelling things.
[all laughing]
[whistling]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a lovely sunny morning,
and Daddy Pig is reading his newspaper.
[Daddy Pig whistling]
Daddy, what are you doing?
I'm reading the newspaper.
[Daddy Pig whistling]
You're making a funny sound.
-I'm whistling.
-Oh.
Whistling is fun. You should try it.
I don't know how to.
It's easy.
Just put your lips together and blow.
[Daddy pig whistles]
[blows air]
Try making a smaller O shape.
[Peppa blows raspberry]
[both laugh]
Like this. [whistles]
And then you can whistle a tune.
[whistling upbeat tune]
[Peppa blowing air]
[sighs] I've got the wrong kind of mouth.
Your mouth is fine.
You just need to practice.
[blows air]
It's impossible.
It takes time to learn
how to do important things,
like riding a bicycle
or playing the piano.
[snorts] It took me years
to learn how to wiggle my ears.
Wow! [giggles]
[narrator] Mommy Pig is in the kitchen
making cookies.
[blowing air]
What are you doing, Peppa?
I'm learning to whistle.
Oh, I see.
[Peppa blows air]
Mommy, can you whistle?
I don't know. I've never tried.
It takes a lot of practice.
[whistles]
Oh, yes.
[narrator] Mommy Pig can whistle.
You can whistle
because you are old, Mommy.
Thank you, Peppa.
[Peppa blowing air]
Vrrroom!
[narrator] George is in the bedroom
playing with his toy rocket.
Vrrroom!
George, I'm learning to whistle.
You make an O shape with your mouth
and blow.
Don't worry, George.
It's almost impossible,
like wiggling your ears.
[narrator] George can wiggle his ears.
[giggling]
[snorts] Whistling is harder.
[whistles]
[narrator] George can whistle.
Oh.
[George whistles]
[giggles]
-[sighs]
-What's wrong, Peppa?
[snorts] I can't whistle,
but everybody else can.
Never mind. I'm making cookies.
Would you like to lick the spoon?
No, thank you, Mommy.
[snorts] Can I ring Suzy Sheep instead?
Okay, Peppa.
[rings]
[bleats] Hello, Mrs. Pig.
Hello, Mrs. Sheep.
Can Peppa talk to Suzy, please?
Hello, Suzy.
[bleats] Hello, Peppa. What are you doing?
I'm learning to whistle,
but I can't do it yet.
Hmm. That sounds hard.
It's impossible.
Uh, can you whistle, Suzy?
No.
[snorts] Oh, good. I mean,
that's sad if you can't whistle,
but good because I can't whistle.
What's whistling, anyway?
You put your lips together and blow.
Like this?
[whistles]
[dial tone humming]
Hello? Peppa?
The cookies are ready!
-Oh, goody. Cookies!
-[George snorts]
They'll be hot.
You should blow on them first.
Ooh, ah. [blows air]
[giggles, then blows air]
-Do you not want a cookie, Peppa?
-No, thank you, Mommy.
I think I might go outside
and be on my own for a little bit.
[snorts] Can you whistle yet?
It's no use, Daddy.
I'm never going to whistle, ever.
Have you been practicing?
[snorts] Yes, lots. But it doesn't work.
You need a little rest, Peppa.
Here, have a cookie.
It's hot. You should blow.
[whistles]
Oh, what's that?
It sounded like a whistle to me.
[Peppa whistling upbeat tune]
-[Peppa giggles]
-What a lovely tune.
[narrator] Peppa has learned
how to whistle.
[giggles] I can whistle!
[all whistling upbeat tune]
[bell ringing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is a school day.
Children, Dr. Hamster has come
to talk to us today.
Hello, everyone.
[all] Hello, Dr. Hamster.
Dr. Hamster is a vet.
Who knows what a vet does?
[bleats] Vets help sick pets get better.
That's right. And I've brought
some of my pets to show you.
[all] Ooh.
This is Binkie the budgie.
[all] Hello, Binkie.
[woofs] Can I stroke Binkie?
Yes, very gently.
He feels fluffy.
Those are his feathers.
They help him to fly.
[students giggle]
[Dr. Hamster] Flying is how Binkie
gets his exercise.
Can you tell me what else Binkie needs
to stay fit and healthy?
-[snorts] He needs to eat.
-Yes.
-He needs to drink.
-That's right.
-He needs to breathe a bit.
-Very good.
-He needs to sleep.
-Excellent.
[yawns] Sorry, Madame Gazelle.
I overslept.
Oh, Pedro, you do like sleeping.
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
I have got a pet here who loves sleeping.
It's a tortoise.
It's Tiddles the tortoise.
[students] Hello, Tiddles.
Tiddles has slept all through the winter.
[students] Ooh.
Why has he got that shell thing
on his back?
That shell is his house.
It's where he hides if he gets scared.
Would you like to stroke him?
Yes, please.
Don't be scared, Tiddles.
How old is he?
Tiddles is 33.
That's as old as my mom.
But tortoises can live
for a hundred years.
[snorts] That's as old as my grandpa.
Why is he so slow?
He has to carry his house on his back.
Uh, Dr. Hamster,
I think Tiddles is escaping.
He can't go far.
Because he is so slow.
I've got someone else to show you here.
[snorts] Dinosaur.
Oh, George. You always say dinosaur.
Oh, it is a dinosaur.
[students] Ooh.
She's not a dinosaur.
This is Lulu the lizard.
[students] Hello, Lulu.
She's scaley like a dragon.
Can she breathe fire?
No, but she has a very long tongue.
[students] Wow!
Does she sleep through the winter
like Tiddles?
No. Oh, where is Tiddles?
Tiddles?
[narrator] Oh, dear.
Tiddles the tortoise has run away.
Don't worry, Dr. Hamster,
we'll find Tiddles.
Is he in the music room?
[narrator] Tiddles is not
in the music room.
Is he in the playhouse?
[narrator] Tiddles is not
in the playhouse.
Is he hiding by the coats?
[narrator] Tiddles is not hiding
by the coats.
[sniffs]
I can smell Tiddles. This way. [sniffing]
[narrator] Freddy Fox has
a very good sense of smell.
There's Tiddles!
[narrator] Tiddles is up a tree.
Oh, I'd better call for help.
[narrator] This is
Miss Rabbit's Fire Station.
[screams] Fire! Fire!
Fire station. Where's the fire?
My Tiddles is up a tree.
[Miss Rabbit] What? Again?
Emergency! Emergency!
Tortoise up a tree!
I don't know why
you like climbing trees so much.
You're a tortoise.
[siren wailing]
Stand back.
Tiddles. [clicks tongue]
Come on, Tiddles.
[students] Hooray!
Thank you, Miss Rabbit.
Just doing my job.
And my job is looking after pets.
Where are Binkie and Lulu?
Oh, I don't know.
Ah-ho. Here they are. Safe and sound.
[all laughing]
[Peppa reads on-screen text]
[narrator] It is bedtime
for Peppa and George.
Tomorrow we're going on a coach trip
to the seaside.
[snorts] We can make sand castles.
-I fancy a swim.
-Me, too.
The weather forecast says
it's going to be sunny.
Good night, Peppa. Good night, George.
[narrator] Oh, it is starting to snow.
[rooster crows]
[narrator] It is morning.
Yippee! It's sunny!
[gasps] Snow!
[narrator] A lot of snow has fallen
in the night.
Snow, Mommy. Snow, Daddy.
Snow, snow, snow!
-[George giggles]
-Eh? What?
We are still going to the seaside,
aren't we?
Well, let's see how much snow there is.
Oh, where's Daddy gone?
[gasps] It's a walking snowman!
[Daddy Pig in muffled voice] I'm cold.
[giggles] It's a walking, talking snowman!
[Daddy Pig shivers]
Oh, it's just Daddy.
Poor Daddy. Let's warm you up.
[all laughing]
[narrator] Mommy Pig, Peppa and George
are warming Daddy Pig up
by rubbing him with towels.
That's better.
[snorts] Now we can go to the seaside.
But what about the snow?
I don't think
the coach will be running today.
Oh.
[bell dings]
[narrator] Miss Rabbit's coach has arrived
at Peppa's house.
[snorts] Goodness me.
How did you get through all that snow?
With my big snowplow.
[narrator] Snowplows push the snow
out of the way.
Hello, everyone.
[children] Hello, Peppa.
[narrator] All of Peppa's friends
are going to the seaside, too.
[bell dings]
Next stop, the seaside.
[passengers] Hooray!
[narrator] Mr. Bull and his friends
are gritting the road.
The grit melts the snow.
Hello, Mr. Bull.
[moos] Hello, Miss Rabbit.
It's taken us all night,
but the road is clear
all the way to seaside.
That's good. We're going to the seaside.
Would you like to come along?
No, thanks, Miss Rabbit. [sniffs]
We've got more roads to grit.
-[passengers] Goodbye, Mr. Bull.
-Bye! Have a lovely day at the beach.
♪ We're all going on a seaside holiday ♪
♪ Sand castles, swimming and sunny skies ♪
♪ Sea and sand and ice cream, too ♪
-[passengers laugh]
-[bell dings]
Here we are, the seaside!
[narrator] The beach is covered in snow.
-[all] Oh!
-That sea looks cold.
-I was looking forward to having a swim.
-You still can. The sea's not frozen over.
Come along, girls.
What are you waiting for?
Um... I can't swim,
because I've sprained my ankle.
And I think I might have a cough. [coughs]
Come on in, Mommy Pig. It's lovely.
Are you sure it's lovely?
-Of course. The sea is wonderful today.
-Okay, then.
[narrator] Mommy Pig is going for a swim.
-[yelps]
-Is it cold, Mommy?
It's a little bit cold.
It always feels cold
when you first get in.
If you keep moving, you'll warm up.
Okay. I'll keep moving.
[narrator] Mommy Pig has run
out of the sea.
Let's get you dry.
[narrator] Peppa, George and Daddy Pig
are warming Mommy Pig up
by rubbing her with towels.
Ah, that's better.
Are you going for a swim, Daddy Pig?
Maybe not today.
-Who wants an ice cream?
-[children] Me!
[narrator] Everyone likes ice creams
at the seaside.
[snorts] I wanted to make sand castles.
But the beach is covered in snow.
[snorts] We can make snow castles.
[children] Ooh.
First, we fill the buckets with snow.
[all giggling]
We turn the buckets upside down,
give them a little tap,
and, hey, presto, a snow castle!
[all] Snow castles!
I love the seaside.
And I love the snow.
I love the seaside and the snow.
[all laughing]
♪ We're all going on a seaside holiday ♪
♪ Sand castles, swimming and sunny skies ♪
♪ Sea and sand and ice cream, too ♪